Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1985-1986, 1983-2004; Accession 2012-M-058
  - Apartment House, Fan Pier Development (Boston, MA) (86059), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 26, Folder 573)
      - Authorities (Box 27, Folder 574)
      - Boston Redevelopment Authority (Box 27, Folder 575)
      - Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 576)
      - Program Background (Box 27, Folder 577)
      - Project Binder (Box 27, Folder 578)
      - Publicity (Box 27, Folder 579)
      - Square Footages (Box 27, Folder 581)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 86)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 109)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 109)
      - Progress Sets (Box 109)
      - Record Mylars (Box 109)
      - Record Set (Box 110)
      - Small Drawings (Box 27, Folder 580)
    - Project Sketches (Box 144, Folder 142)
  - Pershing Square Competition (Los Angeles, CA) (86061), Project Images, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - Chestnut Hill Residence (Brookline, MA) (86063), 1986 - 1991
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 27, Folder 582)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 27, Folder 583)
      - Authorities (Box 27, Folder 584)
      - Contracts (Box 27, Folder 585)
      - Field Reports (Box 27, Folder 586)
      - Hardware (Box 27, Folder 587)
      - Interiors - Furnishings (1) (Box 27, Folder 588)
      - Interiors - Furnishings (2) (Box 27, Folder 589)
      - Interiors - Furnishings (3) (Box 27, Folder 590)
      - Interiors - Furnishings (4) (Box 27, Folder 591)
      - Interiors - Furnishings (5) (Box 28, Folder 592)
      - Interiors - Project Binder (Box 28, Folder 593)
      - Landscape (Box 28, Folder 595)
      - Legal (Box 28, Folder 596)
      - Lighting (Box 28, Folder 597)
      - Mechanical (Box 28, Folder 598)
      - Memoranda (Box 29, Folder 599)
      - Notes (Box 29, Folder 600)
      - Pool Grilles (Box 29, Folder 601)
      - Prices (Box 29, Folder 602)
      - Project Manual (Box 29, Folder 603)
      - Punch Lists (Box 29, Folder 604)
      - Rails (Box 29, Folder 605)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 29, Folder 606)
      - Specifications (Box 29, Folder 608)
      - Urns (Box 29, Folder 609)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 42, Folder 88)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 42, Folder 89)
    - Project Images (3) (Box 42, Folder 90)
    - Project Images (4) (Box 42, Folder 91)
    - Project Drawings
      - Color Studies (Box 110)
      - Interiors - Small Drawings (Box 28, Folder 594)
      - Monograph Drawings (Box 110)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1986 (Box 110)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 (Box 111)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1989 (Box 111)
      - Site Surveys (Box 111)
      - Small Drawings (Box 29, Folder 607)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 149)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 150)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings, 1988-1989 (Box 145, Folder 151)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings, 1990-1991 (Box 145, Folder 152)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Cabinetry (Box 145, Folder 153)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Furnishings (Box 145, Folder 154)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Sketches (Box 145, Folder 155)
      - Working Drawings - Part 1 (Box 112)
      - Working Drawings - Part 2 (Box 113)
      - Working Drawings - Part 3 (Box 113)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor plans, Site plans (Box 144, Folder 143)
      - Sketches - Gazebo (Box 144, Folder 144)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 144, Folder 145)
      - Sketches - Mouldings (Box 145, Folder 146)
      - Sketches - Pool Area (Box 145, Folder 147)
      - Sketches - Presentation (Box 145, Folder 148)
  - Renovations to a Residence in Edgartown (Martha's Vineyard, MA) (86066), 1986 - 1988
    35mm slides for this project label it as phase II of project number 84215.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 30, Folder 610)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 30, Folder 611)
      - Chimney (Box 30, Folder 612)
      - Hardware (Box 30, Folder 613)
      - Kitchen (Box 30, Folder 614)
      - Lighting (Box 30, Folder 615)
      - Master Bathroom (Box 30, Folder 616)
      - Memoranda (Box 30, Folder 617)
      - Notes (Box 30, Folder 618)
      - Punch Lists (Box 30, Folder 619)
      - Structural (Box 30, Folder 621)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 92)
    - Project Drawings
      - Small Drawings (Box 30, Folder 620)
      - Working Drawings (Box 114)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 146, Folder 156)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 146, Folder 157)
      - Sketches - Presentation (Box 146, Folder 158)
  - Residence at Conyers Farm (Greenwich, CT) (86067), 1986 - 1989
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 30, Folder 622)
      - Equipment (Box 30, Folder 623)
      - Memoranda (Box 30, Folder 624)
      - Notes (Box 30, Folder 625)
      - Program Background (Box 30, Folder 626)
      - Specifications (Box 30, Folder 628)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 42, Folder 93)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 42, Folder 94)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 114)
      - Progress Set (Box 114)
      - Site Surveys (Box 115)
      - Small Drawings (Box 30, Folder 627)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 146, Folder 160)
      - Working Drawings (Box 115)
    - Project Sketches (Box 146, Folder 159)
  - Breckenridge Legal (Breckenridge, CO) (86068), Project File, 1986 - 1987 (Box 30, Folder 629)
    See Also: 85012 -- Breckenridge Development 85038 -- Breckenridge Swan Valley Lodge 85039 -- Breckenridge Temporary Clubhouse 85069 -- Breckenridge Golf Club.
  - Alterations to the Catlin House (Greenwich, CT) (86069), Project Drawings, 1986 - 1987 (Box 115)
    See Also: 84258 - Catlin Renovations.
  - Residence on Prospect Avenue (Hartford, CT) (86070), 1986 - 1988
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 30, Folder 630)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 30, Folder 631)
      - Contract (Box 30, Folder 632)
      - Doors and Windows (Box 30, Folder 633)
      - Memoranda (Box 30, Folder 634)
      - Program Background (Box 30, Folder 635)
      - Roofing (Box 30, Folder 636)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 30, Folder 637)
    - Project Images (Box 42, Folder 95)
    - Project Drawings (Box 115)
    - Project Sketches (Box 146, Folder 161)
  - Center For Jewish Life, Princeton University (Princeton, NJ (86071), 1986 - 1993
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 30, Folder 638)
      - Architect/Construction Manager - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 639)
      - Architect/Construction Manager - Cost Analysis (Box 31, Folder 640)
      - Architect/Construction Manager - Extra Work Authorization (Box 31, Folder 641)
      - Architect/Construction Manager - Memoranda (Box 31, Folder 642)
      - Authorities (Box 31, Folder 643)
      - Civil (Box 31, Folder 644)
      - Construction Log 1 (Box 31, Folder 645)
      - Construction Log 2 (Box 31, Folder 646)
      - Construction Log 3 (Box 31, Folder 647)
      - Construction Log 4 (Box 31, Folder 648)
      - Construction Log 5 (Box 31, Folder 649)
      - Construction Log 6 (Box 31, Folder 650)
      - Contract (Box 31, Folder 651)
      - Drawing Schedule (Box 31, Folder 652)
      - Equipment (Box 32, Folder 653)
      - Field Reports (Box 32, Folder 654)
      - Food Service (Box 32, Folder 655)
      - Interiors (Box 32, Folder 656)
      - Lighting (Box 32, Folder 657)
      - Mechanical (Box 32, Folder 658)
      - Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 659)
      - Project Binder (Box 32, Folder 660)
      - Publicity (Box 32, Folder 661)
      - RFI Log (Box 32, Folder 662)
      - Site Information (Box 32, Folder 663)
      - Specifications - Volume 1 (Box 32, Folder 665)
      - Specifications - Volume 2 (Box 32, Folder 666)
      - Structural (Box 32, Folder 667)
    - 86071 Project Images (1) (Box 42, Folder 96)
    - 86071 Project Images (2) (Box 43, Folder 97)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 116)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 116)
      - Measured Drawings of Existing Building (Box 116)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 116)
      - Small Drawings (Box 32, Folder 664)
      - Small-Scale Presentation Drawings (Box 146, Folder 166)
      - Working Drawings - Design Development (Box 117)
      - Working Drawings - Part 1 (Box 117)
      - Working Drawings - Part 2 (Box 118)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Details (Box 146, Folder 162)
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans, Sections (Box 146, Folder 163)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 146, Folder 164)
      - Sketches - Perspectives (Box 146, Folder 165)
  - Fine Arts Studio IV, University of California, Irvine (Irvine, CA) (86072), 1986 - 1989
    See Also: 86037 - Master Plan, Fine Arts Village, University of California, Irvine 88062 - Humanities Master Plan, University of California, Irvine.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Architect (Box 32, Folder 668)
      - Architect/Client (Box 33, Folder 669)
      - Architect/Consultants (Box 33, Folder 670)
      - Authorities (Box 33, Folder 671)
      - Electrical (Box 33, Folder 672)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 33, Folder 673)
      - Fees (Box 33, Folder 674)
      - Interiors (Box 33, Folder 675)
      - Landscape (Box 33, Folder 676)
      - Lighting (Box 33, Folder 677)
      - Mechanical (Box 33, Folder 678)
      - Memoranda (Box 33, Folder 679)
      - Prices (Box 33, Folder 680)
      - Program Background (Box 33, Folder 681)
      - Project Binder (Box 33, Folder 682)
      - Project Manual (Box 33, Folder 683)
      - Publicity (Box 33, Folder 684)
      - Specifications (Box 33, Folder 685)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 98)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 118)
      - Record Set (Box 119)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 146, Folder 168)
    - Project Sketches (Box 146, Folder 167)
  - 222 Berkeley Street (Boston, MA) (86073), 1986 - 1991
    - Project File
      - Architect/Architect (Box 33, Folder 686)
      - Architect/Client (Box 33, Folder 687)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 34, Folder 688)
      - Atrium (Box 34, Folder 689)
      - Boston Redevelopment Authority - Environmental Impact Report (Box 34, Folder 690)
      - Boston Redevelopment Authority - Schematic Design Submission (Box 34, Folder 691)
      - Coulton Building (Box 34, Folder 692)
      - FAO Schwartz Entrance (Box 34, Folder 693)
      - Fees (Box 34, Folder 694)
      - Memoranda - Design Advisory Panel (Box 34, Folder 695)
      - Memoranda - Jung/Brannen (Box 34, Folder 696)
      - Memoranda - Kendall/Heaton (Box 34, Folder 697)
      - Memoranda - RAMSA (Box 34, Folder 698)
      - Notes (1) (Box 34, Folder 699)
      - Notes (2) (Box 35, Folder 700)
      - Program Background (Box 35, Folder 701)
      - Project Manual - Volume 1 (Box 35, Folder 702)
      - Project Manual - Volume 2 (Box 35, Folder 703)
      - Project Manual - Volume 3 (Box 35, Folder 704)
      - Project Manual - Volume 4 (Box 35, Folder 705)
      - Publicity (Box 35, Folder 706)
      - Site Information (Box 35, Folder 707)
      - Specifications (Box 35, Folder 709)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 43, Folder 99)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 43, Folder 100)
    - Project Drawings
      - Color Studies (Box 119)
      - Design Drawings - Mylar (Box 120)
      - Design Drawings - Vellum, 1986-1987 (Box 120)
      - Design Drawings - Vellum, 1988 (Box 121)
      - Monograph Drawing (Box 121)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1986 November 13 (Box 121)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 January 20 (Box 121)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 March 30 (Box 122)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 July 15 (Box 122)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 September 15 (Box 123)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 November 20 (Box 123)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 December 18 (Box 123)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1988 April 25 (Box 122)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1989 February 10 (Box 122)
      - Record Sets (Box 124)
      - Small Drawings (Box 35, Folder 708)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches by -- RAMS (Box 147, Folder 169)
      - Sketches - By Timothy Lenahan (Box 147, Folder 170)
      - Sketches - Details and Studies (Box 147, Folder 171)
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans, Sections (Box 147, Folder 172)
      - Sketches - Elevator (Box 147, Folder 173)
      - Sketches - First Presentation (Box 147, Folder 174)
      - Sketches - Grand Stair (Box 147, Folder 175)
      - Sketches - Light Fixtures (Box 147, Folder 176)
      - Sketches - Lobbies (Box 147, Folder 177)
      - Sketches - Street Entrances/Storefronts (Box 147, Folder 178)
  - Essex Bay Estates (West Gloucester, MA) (86074), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File (Box 35, Folder 710)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 101)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 125)
      - Site Surveys (Box 125)
    - Project Sketches (Box 147, Folder 179)
  - Kiluna Farm Houses (North Hills, NY) (86075), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 35, Folder 711)
      - Civil (Box 35, Folder 712)
      - Landscape (Box 36, Folder 713)
      - Lighting (Box 36, Folder 714)
      - Marketing Directors (Box 36, Folder 715)
      - Mechanical (Box 36, Folder 716)
      - Memoranda (Box 36, Folder 717)
      - Notes (Box 36, Folder 718)
      - Research (Box 36, Folder 719)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 36, Folder 720)
      - Specifications (Box 36, Folder 722)
      - Structural (Box 36, Folder 723)
      - Tennis House (Box 36, Folder 724)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 102)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 125)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 125)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 126)
      - Record Sepias (Box 126)
      - Site Surveys (Box 126)
      - Small Drawings (Box 36, Folder 721)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 147, Folder 182)
      - Working Drawings (Box 126)
      - Working Drawings - Preliminary (Box 127)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Floor Plans (Box 147, Folder 180)
      - Sketches - Site Plans (Box 147, Folder 181)
  - Patricof Apartment (New York, NY) (86077), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 82151 - Patricof Apartment.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 36, Folder 725)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 36, Folder 726)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 36, Folder 727)
      - Authorities (Box 36, Folder 728)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 36, Folder 729)
      - Memoranda (Box 36, Folder 730)
      - Prices (Box 36, Folder 731)
      - Punch List (Box 36, Folder 732)
      - Skylight (Box 36, Folder 733)
      - Windows (Box 36, Folder 735)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 103)
    - Project Drawings
      - Color Studies (Box 127)
      - Light Fixture for Bath and Toilet (Box 127)
      - Small Drawings (Box 36, Folder 734)
      - Working Drawings (Box 127)
    - Project Sketches (Box 147, Folder 183)
  - Milwin Farm: Tennis Pavilion (Ocean Township, NJ) (86078), 1986 - 1987
    See Also: 85093 - Milwin Farm 86018 - Milwin Farm: Gatehouse and Poolhouse.
    - Project Drawings (Box 128)
    - Project Sketches (Box 148, Folder 184)
  - Wynnewood Houses (Stamford, CT) (86082), 1986 - 1988
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 36, Folder 736)
      - Architect/Consultant (Box 36, Folder 737)
      - Contracts (Box 36, Folder 738)
      - Fact Sheets (Box 36, Folder 739)
      - House 1 (Box 36, Folder 740)
      - House 2 (Box 36, Folder 741)
      - House 3 (Box 36, Folder 742)
      - House 4 (Box 36, Folder 743)
      - Juner Properties (Box 36, Folder 744)
      - Memoranda (Box 36, Folder 745)
      - Prices (Box 36, Folder 746)
      - Project Binder (Box 36, Folder 747)
      - Publicity (Box 36, Folder 748)
      - Research (Box 36, Folder 749)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 37, Folder 750)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 43, Folder 104)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 43, Folder 105)
    - Project Drawings
      - House 1 - Working Drawings (Box 128)
      - House 2 - Working Drawings (Box 128)
      - House 3 - Working Drawings (Box 128)
      - House 4 - Working Drawings (Box 129)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 129)
      - Record Sets (Box 129)
      - Site Surveys (Box 130)
      - Small Drawings (Box 37, Folder 751)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 148, Folder 192)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - House 1 (Box 148, Folder 185)
      - Sketches - House 2 (Box 148, Folder 186)
      - Sketches - House 3 (Box 148, Folder 187)
      - Sketches - House 4 (Box 148, Folder 188)
      - Sketches - House 5 (Box 148, Folder 189)
      - Sketches - House 6 (Box 148, Folder 190)
      - Sketches - Perspectives (Box 148, Folder 191)
  - Winchester Country Club (Winchester, VA) (86083), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 37, Folder 752)
      - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 753)
      - Program Background (Box 37, Folder 754)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 106)
    - Project Drawings (Box 130)
    - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 149, Folder 195)
    - Small-Scale Presentation Drawings (Box 149, Folder 193)
    - Project Sketches (Box 149, Folder 194)
  - Apartment Tower, Union Theological Seminary (New York, NY) (86084), 1986 - 1987
    See Also: 87006 - Manhattan School of Music.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 37, Folder 755)
      - Interiors (Box 37, Folder 756)
      - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 757)
      - Notes (Box 37, Folder 758)
      - Publicity (Box 37, Folder 759)
      - Response to Request for Proposal (Box 37, Folder 760)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 107)
    - Project Drawings
      - Demolition Plans (Box 130)
      - Design Drawings (Box 130)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 February 20 (Box 131)
      - Presentation Drawings, 1987 December 15 (Box 131)
      - Record Sepias (Box 131)
      - Site Plans (Box 131)
      - Small Drawings (Box 37, Folder 761)
    - Project Sketches (Box 149, Folder 196)
  - Swid Powell Series II (86085), 1986 - 1988
    See Also: 82172 - Swid Powell Tableware.
    - Project File
      - Color Samples (Box 37, Folder 762)
      - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 763)
      - Orders/Statements (Box 37, Folder 764)
      - Publicity (Box 37, Folder 765)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 108)
    - Project Drawings (Box 132)
    - Small Drawings (Box 37, Folder 766)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Candlesticks (Box 149, Folder 197)
      - Sketches - Ice Bucket (Box 149, Folder 198)
      - Sketches - Mantle Clock (Box 149, Folder 199)
  - Upper East Side Apartment (New York, NY) (86086), 1986 - 1987
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 37, Folder 767)
      - Interiors (Box 37, Folder 768)
      - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 769)
      - Prices (Box 37, Folder 770)
    - Project Images (Box 43, Folder 109)
    - Project Drawings
      - Small Drawings (Box 37, Folder 771)
      - Working Drawings (Box 149, Folder 200)
  - Copperflagg: Sciandra House Interiors (New York, NY) (86089), Project File, 1986 - 1987 (Box 37, Folder 772)
    See Also: 85006 - 81 Copperflagg Lane.
  - Ottinger House (Martha's Vineyard, MA) (86090), 1986 - 1987
    See Also: 83205 - Ottinger House.
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 37, Folder 773)
      - Authorities (Box 37, Folder 774)
      - Legal (Box 37, Folder 775)
      - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 776)
      - Notes (Box 37, Folder 777)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 37, Folder 778)
    - Project Drawings
      - Progress Set (Box 132)
      - Working Drawings (Box 132)
- Project records for 1987-1989, 1987-2001; Accession 2014-M-052
  - Townhouse Apartment (New York, NY) (87001), 1987-1988
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Project drawings (Box 65)
  - Owligorical House for Parish Art Museum (Southampton, NY) (87003), 1987
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Project drawings (Box 65)
  - Carnegie Hill Townhouse (New York, NY) (87004), 1987-1990
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 3-16)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies, monograph, and presentation drawings (Box 65)
      - Record sets and working drawings (Box 66)
    - Project sketches (Box 153, Folder 1-4)
  - Residence at Brainard Woods (West Hartford, CT) (87005), 1987-1989
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Project drawings (Box 67)
    - Project sketches (Box 153, Folder 5-6)
  - Claremont Tower, Manhattan School of Music (New York, NY) (87006), 1987-1988
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 18-25)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Project drawings (Box 67)
    - Project sketches (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - South Dartmouth Office Building (South Dartmouth, MA) (87007), 1987
    - Project Images (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Project drawings (Box 68)
  - Sailors' Snug Harbor Music Halls Competition (Staten Island, NY) (87008), 1987
    - Project file (Box 2, Folder 26-33)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings and progress prints (Box 68)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Project sketches (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Decorative Arts for Munari Design Associati (87009), 1987-1989
    - Project file (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Project drawings (Box 68)
  - Pierson Property (Marion, MA) (87010), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Skyview (Aspen, CO) (87011), 1987-1990
    See Also: 95034
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, memoranda, field reports, and miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 36-50)
      - Approvals, mechanical, millwork, job books, and miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 51-59)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 9-11)
    - Project drawings
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Small drawings (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Color studies (Box 68)
      - Monograph and presentation drawings (Box 69)
      - Record sets (Box 70)
      - Working drawings (1) (Box 72)
      - Working drawings (2) (Box 73)
    - Project sketches
      - Details (Box 154, Folder 10)
      - Apr 1987-Oct 1987 (Box 71)
  - Chera, Brooklyn (Brooklyn, NY) (87012), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Casting Center, Walt Disney World (Lake Buena Vista, FL) (87013), 1987-1989
    - Project file
      - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 61-69)
      - Correspondence, minutes, specifications, etc. (Box 4, Folder 70-89)
      - Correspondence, change orders, publicity, etc. (Box 5, Folder 90-95)
    - Project images (Box 53, Folder 12-14)
    - Project drawings
      - Monograph and presentation drawings (Box 73)
      - Record sets and Sk's (Box 74)
      - Working drawings (Box 74)
      - Small-scale design and presentation drawings (Box 154, Folder 13-14)
    - Project sketches (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Ohrstrom Library, St. Paul's School (Concord, NH) (87014), 1987-1991
    See Also: 85094
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and publicity (Box 5, Folder 96-105)
      - Contracts, furnishings, specifications, and miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 106-123)
      - Change orders, job books, project binder, and miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 124-135)
    - Project images
      - Project Images (1) (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Project images (2-5) (Box 54, Folder 16-19)
    - Project drawings
      - Code analysis plans and color studies (Box 75)
      - Construction schedules, monograph, and presentation drawings (Box 76)
      - Working drawings, A1-A103, T1 (Box 77)
      - Working drawings (Box 78)
      - Working drawings (preliminary) (Box 79)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Project sketches
      - Elevations, plans, details, and furnishings (Box 155, Folder 15-20)